准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
伟大的
蜗牛比赛
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
早安  菠萝屋
Good morning, pineapple
小蜗
早安  小蜗
Good morning, Gary
早安  全世界
Good morning, world
我准备好了
I'm ready
世界
World?
有话快说
Talk to me
包裹到了
Package, sir
居然真的到了
I can't believe it's finally here
拿去吧
There you go
谢谢谢谢谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you
感谢  你是
Thank you, Mr.
章鱼东东包吧
Tennis Balls
那是章鱼哥
That's "Tentacles"
原来那就是章鱼哥的大名啊
Squidward's last name is "Tentacles"?
真可怜
Poor guy
快看章鱼哥新养的蜗牛
Check out Squidward's new snail
好高贵
Fancy
原来你收到的是这个啊
So that's what came in the mail
看来小蜗有新玩伴了
Looks like Gary has a new little playmate
痴心妄想  海绵宝宝
Dream on, SpongeBob
斯纳丽绝对不准跟那头杂种玩
I wouldn't let Snellie here play with that mongrel mutt
它可是纯种的
She's a purebred
面包做的蜗牛
A snail made out of bread
[ bread（面包）与 purebred（纯种）谐音 ]
不对
No
纯种意思就是血统高贵
Purebred means she's of the highest pedigree
看见没
See?
血统证明
斯纳丽
饲主  章鱼哥
连专属的证明文件都有
She even has her own papers
那就先失陪了
So if you'll excuse us
斯纳丽要开始训练了
Snellie has to start her training
干嘛训练
Training?
准备裤头村蜗牛比赛啊
For Bikini Bottom's snail race
斯纳丽这周天肯定能获胜
Snellie will be winning this Sunday
周天
Sunday?
看来没办法让小蜗参赛了
Well, I guess I can't enter Gary in that
周天得洗衣服
Sunday's laundry day
不对  海绵宝宝
No, SpongeBob
之所以没法参赛  是因为小蜗是杂种
You can't enter Gary because Gary's a mutt
你说得对
Boy, you got that right
小蜗没
Gary's no
你凭什么这么确定小蜗没法获胜
What makes you so sure Gary couldn't win that race?
文件
Papers
饲主
章鱼哥
饲主  章鱼大脓包
"Property of Squidward Pimples"
那叫东东包
That's Tennisball
章鱼哥
Tentacles
走了  斯纳丽
Come on, Snellie
跟你说
You know what?
我开始有点理解
I'm starting to get the idea
章鱼哥说他家蜗牛比我家好了
that Squidward thinks his snail is better than mine
不会吧
No
派大星  你想的跟我一样吗
Patrick, are you thinking what I'm thinking?
对  我得去找个蜗牛来
Yeah, I should get a snail
让它参赛  打败章鱼哥
and enter it in that race and beat Squidward
你想的跟我一样吗
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
不对不对不对
No, no, no
我想的是要让你参赛
I'm thinking about entering you in that race
打败章鱼哥家的蜗牛
and beating Squidward's snail
看来现在得开始训练了  小妹妹
Looks like we're going to start our training now, ladies
叫你小妹妹是要让你丢脸
I call you a lady to humiliate and demean you
教练就用这种话来激励大伙儿
It's a motivational tool we coaches use
不知道为什么
I don't know why
明天一定得把海绵宝宝揍一顿
but I think I'll kick SpongeBob's butt tomorrow
海草粉  吃了多长肌肉
Kelp powder for muscle mass
生蛋  老套路最好用
raw eggs 'cause they're cliche
钉子
还有钉子  增进体魄
and nails for toughness
当然得让你吃啊
Of course I expect you to eat this
这可是科学配方  保证让你明天获胜
It's scientifically designed to help you win tomorrow
小蜗
Gary?
跑得挺快
Pretty good time
海绵宝宝  快看我新养的蜗牛
Hey, SpongeBob, check out my new snail
派大星  你家蜗牛是石头
Patrick, your snail is a rock
没错  谢谢
Yeah, thanks
这我知道
I know
它有着钢铁一样的意志
He's got nerves of steel
大赛见了
See you at the big race
天啊  竞争越来越激烈了
Boy, the competition's getting tough
就这样了  小蜗
That's it, Gary
马上开始高强度训练
We are going to start some serious training right now
小蜗  先从冲刺开始练
All right, Gary, let's start with some sprints
各就各位  预备
On your mark, set
跑
go
小蜗跑起来
Go, Gary, go
加油
come on
小蜗跑啊
Go, Gary
胜利属于你  小蜗
It's all yours, Gary
小蜗
Gary?
真是的  小蜗
Come on, Gary
明天就要比赛了
the big race is tomorrow
要赢就得马上训练
You got to start training if you want to win
别白费口舌了  海绵宝宝
Don't waste your breath, SpongeBob
你家杂种绝对赢不过我家斯纳丽
That mongrel of yours
doesn't have a chance against Snellie
不好意思
Excuse me
你们两个好像忘了
but you two seem to be forgetting
真正的赢家得主会是
who the real winner will be
我家的蜗牛
My snail
派大星  那是石头
Patrick, that's a rock
没错  谢谢
Yeah, thanks
我知道
I know
它有着钢铁一样的意志
He's got nerves of steel
你站哪来着
What are you standing on, anyway?
我刚刚说过
Like I said
不用麻烦你明天来参赛了
don't even bother showing up tomorrow
我家蜗牛把章鱼哥给吓坏了
My snail's really got Squidward scared
对吧  海绵宝宝
huh, SpongeBob?
抱歉  派大星
Sorry, Patrick
我跟小蜗得去高强度训练了
Gary and I've got some serious work to do
你可以逃得走
You can run
但绝对躲不掉  海绵宝宝
but you can't hide, Squarepants
小蜗  不能再闹下去了
All right, Gary, no more fooling around
要来认真训练
Time to get serious
小蜗  快点动起来
Come on, Gary, move it
上上上上
Up, up, up, up
下下下下
Down, down, down, down
蛞蝓兄弟
快快快
Faster, faster, faster
冲冲冲
Go, go, go
快点加把劲
Come on, push it
小蜗  加把劲
Gary, push it
壳给我动起来
Move that shell
小蜗  动作快
Come on, Gary, move it
冲刺
Let's go
快点
Faster
冲刺
Let's go
加速
Speed it up
动作快  小蜗
Move it, Gary
快快快
Move it, move it, move it
动起来动起来
Stroke, stroke, stroke
动作快  小蜗
Come on, Gary
蜗牛比赛  牡蛎体育场
比赛就要迟到了
we're going to be late for the big race
为快而生
我爱
裤头村
下午好  女士们先生们
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen
欢迎收看现场直播
and welcome to our live coverage
观赏今年春季必看经典
of this year's spring classic
第102届蜗牛赛跑
the 102nd Running of The Snail
今天天气正好来举办这王牌运动
And what a beautiful day for this sport of kings
而我刚好就是狂热体育迷
of which I'm a huge fan
说真的  我就只是个体育迷
Seriously, I'm just a fan
本来要找到座位坐的  结果这门开着
I was on my way to my seat, the door was open
你干什么
What are you doing?
不好意思
Sorry about that, folks
一起把目光投向场上
Let's go down to the field
看市长主持开幕式
to join the mayor for the pre-game ceremony
现在来点燃象征体育精神的圣火
And now for the lighting
of the Torch of Good Sportsmanship
请大家跟我
Please join me
一起欢迎蜗牛比赛第一届冠军
in welcoming snail racing's first-ever champion
闪电拉里卢西安诺
Lightning Larry Luciano
大家请看
Would you look at that, folks?
闪电拉里卢西安诺  活生生的传奇
Lightning Larry Luciano, a living legend
正缓慢走向场地正中央
slowly making his way center stage
这可是这项运动的高光时刻
And what a proud moment for this sport
全场观众欣喜若狂
The crowd is going absolutely nuts
庆贺拉里
for Larry
它就快到了
He's almost there
没错
Yes, siree
随时都会抵达
Any minute now
两小时后
它已经快走四分之一的路程了
He's almost a quarter of the way there
圣火点燃了
The torch is lit
比赛开始
Let the race begin
海绵宝宝  不得不承认
Well, SpongeBob, I must admit
想不到你家杂种
I didn't think that mongrel mutt of yours
居然还能找到起点线
would even find the starting line
恭喜你了
Congratulations
等你输了再来恭喜  章鱼哥
Save it for the loser's circle, Squidward
小蜗现在状态好到不能再好了
Gary happens to be in the best shape of his life
我会提醒现场医生的
I'll alert the paramedics
真好笑  章鱼哥
Good one, Squidward
准备好了吗
You guys ready?
有小偷
A burglar
不对  派大星
No, Patrick
那是裁判
that's the official
已经做好开赛准备了
We're ready to start here, folks
好了  斯纳丽
Okay, Snellie
给这些普通蜗牛见识一下
let's show these common, garden-variety snails
优良种有什么本事
what superior breeding is all about
小蜗  听好了
All right, Gary, listen up
等下竞争会特别残酷
The competition is going to be fierce
你现在处于劣势
You're the undersnail
大家都不把你当一回事
Everybody's already counting you out
快上场获胜
Now get out there and win
给章鱼哥好看
so we can rub Squidward's big, fat nose in it
训练那么久就为了这一刻  石头
This is what you've been training for, Rocky
所以我们才会来
This is why we're here
各就各位  预备
On your mark, get set
爬
slither
选手出发了
And they're off
六号选手斯纳丽飞速起跑
Number six, Snellie, rockets out of the starting blocks
把另外两名对手狠狠甩在身后
leaving the other two competitors in the dust
什么
What?
加油  斯纳丽
Go, Snellie
你行的  宝贝
you got it, baby
你干什么  小蜗
What are you doing, Gary?
比赛都开始了
The race has started
斯纳丽都抢先你了
You let Snellie take the lead
快上啊  小蜗
Let's go, Gary
动起来
Start moving
我们训练那么久  都让你搞砸了
You're blowing everything we trained for
搞砸了
Blowing it
没关系  石头
It's okay, Rocky
想出发了再出发
You go when you feel like it
小蜗  你有没有听到
Gary, are you listening to me?
别慢悠悠了  马上加快速度
Get the anchors out of your pants right now
别用那副表情看我
Don't give me that look
我说马上加快
I said now, mister
冲起来  小蜗
Get going, Gary
冲冲冲冲
Go, go, go, go
七号选手已经起跑了
And there goes number seven out of the starting gate
先等一下
Hang on, folks
选手状态似乎不佳
He doesn't look so good
还不行  小蜗
Not good enough, Gary
还不行
Not good enough
快
Faster
这种状态可不太好
I do not like the look of this
快点  小蜗
Come on, Gary
这可是比赛
it's a race
比赛
A race
你是聋了吗
Have you heard of 'em?
教练逼蜗牛逼得太紧了
That coach is pushing that snail too hard
快啊  小蜗
Faster, Gary
快快快快
Faster, faster, faster, faster
七号选手好像爆炸了
Looks like number seven has a blowout
爆炸两次了
Make that two, folks
小蜗
Gary?
头垫片也炸了
Plus a blown head gasket
可怜的蜗牛还在冲向终点
And the poor creature's still going for it
小蜗  可以不用跑了
Gary, you can stop now
它已经失控了
And he's losing control
想喘口气就喘吧  小蜗
You can take a breath now if you want to, Gary
它在失控地转圈
He's spinning out of control
直冲着墙壁撞去
He's heading straight for the wall
不要
No
撑住  小蜗
Hold on, Gary
我来了
I'm coming
一位教练似乎奔向了跑道
One of the coaches seems to have raced onto the track
这样就自动取消比赛资格了
That is an automatic disqualification
终点
看样子六号选手胜券在握了
Looks like number six has this race all wrapped up
女士们先生们
ladies and gentlemen
加油  斯纳丽
Come on, Snellie
场上只剩你了
it's all you, baby
小蜗  真对不起
Oh, Gary, I'm sorry
为什么不早说我逼你逼得太紧了呢
Why didn't you just say I was pushing it too hard?
你早说了
You did?
小蜗  为什么不早说我没在听呢
Oh, Gary, why didn't you tell me I wasn't listening?
你早说了
You did?
小蜗
Oh, Gary
什么
What?
小蜗
Gary?
天啊
My, oh, my
各位观众  这种情况前所未见
Folks, I have never seen anything quite like this
看来遥遥领先的斯纳丽
It seems Snellie, the leader
调头回来安慰小蜗了
just went back to comfort Gary
看来咱俩要当亲家了  章鱼哥
Looks like you and I are in-laws, eh, Squidward?
可是不可能啊
But that's impossible
要是斯纳丽没赢  那
If Snellie didn't win, then
获胜者是石头
And the winner is Rocky
真不敢相信
I can't believe it
我的纯种蜗牛
My purebred
明明花了我一千七
Which cost me $1,700
却输给了一块石头
Lost to a rock
没关系  章鱼哥
Don't worry, Squidward
我知道你特别想赢
I know how much you wanted to win
所以我特地给你刻了奖杯
so I had the trophy engraved to you
好啊  派大星
Gosh, Patrick
谢了
thanks
蜗牛赛跑第一名奖杯
"The 1st Place Snail Racing Cup
献给  章鱼冬冬包
Presented to Squidward Tortellini?"
冬冬包
这还算赢吗
Will I ever win?
谁叫你昨天乱来  海绵宝宝
That's for yesterday, Squarepants
蟹老板的
中年危机
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
您正在收听的是老K电台
You've got it tuned to KOLD
夕阳红专属电台
K-OLD, the all oldies station
接下来的内容
Here's a little something
会让各位听众回忆往日美好时光
you may remember from the good old days
你好老
You're old
老到发发牢骚
Grumbling like a geezer
曾经红极一时  如今行将就木
Yourself a-cracklin' like an old has-been
看看自己  老头
Look at yourself, old man
长着好多层下巴
you've got multiple chins
因为你好老
'Cause you're old
早安  老爸
Good morning, Daddy
我给你做了早餐
I made you breakfast
谢谢  小豆豆
Thank you, sweet pea
麸皮能让你做出这么多花样
I see you got creative with the bran today
张嘴
Open up
来吃药了
It's time for the pill
真见鬼
Barnacles
我恨吃药
I hate the pill
珍珍
Pearl
你觉得我
do you think I'm
老吗
old?
那当然了
Well, of course I do
不过问题不大
But that's okay
老爸本来就该老
Daddies are supposed to be old
可我还是很酷  对吧
But I'm still cool, right?
你老爸酷吧
Your old man is cool?
你看  大伙早都不会说酷这个字了
See, no one says "cool" anymore
老头子才会这么说
That's such an old-person thing
现在都是说炫  举个例子
Now we say "coral," as in
你鼻子整得好炫
"That nose job is so coral"
炫  是吧
"Coral," eh?
你一说就不炫了
When you say it, it sounds so uncoral
不然我抑扬顿挫再念一遍
What if I said it with a different inflection?
炫
Co-ral
你就不用去上班的吗  老爸
Don't you have to go to work or something, Dad?
还真是
You're right
祝你今天超炫  乖女儿
Have a coral day, honey
珍妮  我是珍珍
Jenny, it's Pearl
炫已经过时了
Coral is definitely out
老
Old?
胡思乱想什么啊
What was I thinking?
我才不老
I ain't old
没事  老爷爷
Don't worry, Pops
马路就快过完了
We're almost across the street
给我滚开
Get away from me
我才不要小孩来
I don't need no snot-nosed little
抱歉让你看到那一幕
sorry you had to see that
快点
Come on
走啊
Move it
还能再慢点吗
Could you be any slower?
你转向灯都连开五个街区了
And you've had your blinker on for the last five blocks
先生  可不可以
Hey, Mister, could you
把球扔回这边来
throw the ball back over here?
要不要我跟你们一起玩啊
How's about I join you kids?
没事
That's okay
送给你了
You can keep it
为什么老头子老是这么扫兴
Why do old people always have to ruin the fun?
别插队
No cutting
跟大家一样好好排队
You got to wait your turn like everybody else
裤头村公墓
不要
No
no
我才没你们那么老
I ain't old like you
我才不老
I ain't old
他有什么毛病
What's his problem?
冰淇淋
下一位
Next
蟹堡王
老妈  我的蟹黄堡味道怪怪的
Mommy, my Krabby patty tastes funny
怪不得
Well, no wonder
都已经放老了  风干了
It's all old and dried out
跟那边那位一个样
like that man right there
快扔到它应该去的地方
Now, put that thing where it belongs
垃圾堆里
In the garbage
小蟹黄堡  我们同病相怜
Well, little patty, we're two of a kind
都失去了往日的光辉
We've both lost our luster
这口感比我这老头还柴
So that's what I taste like
早安  蟹堡王的员工们
Good morning, Krusty Crew
嗨  派大星
Hi, Patrick
准备好晚上一起出去玩了吗
You all ready for the big night out tonight?
好了  一定会特好玩
Yeah, it's gonna rock
准备好狂玩了吗
Are you ready to go crazy?
我都已经幻听了
I'm already hearing voices
准备好
Are you ready to
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
派大星
Patrick
能别叫了吗
Do you mind?
我们借一步说话吧  派大星
Let's continue this conversation in private, Patrick
好像有谁在偷听
I think some people are eavesdropping
那种家伙也太没礼貌了
Well, how rude of some people
那俩小伙子晚上要进城大玩特玩
Those youngsters are going out
for a big night on the town
我一整周都可期待今晚的到来了
I've been looking forward to this night all week
狂欢
Party
你说要先玩什么
What do you think we should do first?
哪有什么不该先玩的
What shouldn't we do first?
我们很年轻
We're young
我们有豪车
we've got wheels
前途无量啊
the world is our oyster
海绵宝宝  你肩膀上面有东西
SpongeBob, you got something on your shoulder
小子们
Hey, boys
要来晃晃吗
Hanging out?
对
Yes
我无意间偷听到了你们的大计
I couldn't help overhearing your big plans
不知道你们还能不能
and I was wondering if you had room
今晚再加一位来跟你们一起狂欢
for one more crazy dude tonight, huh?
当然能了
Of course
你要跟我们一起玩吗  蟹老板
Did you want to come with us, Mr. Krabs?
没想到会这么顺利
Hadn't even crossed me mind
好啊
But sure
这就去
I'll go
不好吧  海绵宝宝
I don't know, SpongeBob
他可能会糟蹋了咱的气派
He might cramp our style
气派
Style
来看看他知不知道
Let's see if he knows
秘密酷小子握手式
the secret cool-guy handshake
好
Yeah
我当然知道
'Course I know it
我等着呢
I'm waiting
老头子
old man
真是幸会
How do you do?
很好  你好吗
Fine, and you?
你可以一起来了
All right, you're in
不过我不是很满意
But I'm not happy about it
你通过测试了  蟹老板
You passed the test, Mr. Krabs
太好了
Great
你们几个小子八点钟来我家碰面吧
Why don't you boys show up at my house at 8:00
先提醒一下你  蟹老板
I just want to warn you, Mr. Krabs
我们总会光鲜亮丽地迟到几下
we're always fashionably late
晚上八点零一分
你好啊  蟹老板
Hey, there, Mr. Krabs
准备好狂欢了吗
Are you ready to party
准备好狂欢了
I'm ready to party
准备好狂欢了吗
Are you ready to party?
准备好狂欢了
I'm ready to party
准备好狂欢了吗  海绵宝宝
Are you ready to party, SpongeBob?
准备好狂欢了
I'm ready to party
准备好狂欢了吗  蟹老板
Are you ready to party, Mr. Krabs?
准备好狂欢了
I'm ready to par-tay
准备好狂欢了吗  海绵宝宝
Are you ready to par-tay, SpongeBob
准备好狂欢了
I'm ready to par-tay
准备好狂欢了吗  派大星
Are you ready to par-tay, Patrick?
准备好狂欢了
I'm ready to party
准备好狂欢了吗  蟹老板
Are you ready to party, Mr. Krabs?
准备好狂欢了
I'm ready to party
准备好
Are you ready to
停
Stop it
别吵了
Just stop it
脸都被你丢光了  老爸
You're embarrassing me, Dad
那
So
今晚有啥豪车
what kind of hot rod will we be cruisin' in tonight?
只开厉害的超跑  保证吸引美女
Only the most powerful chick-magnet in town
水下碎心者
the underwater heartbreaker
吓跑美女还差不多
It's more like a chick repellent
座位才两个
And there's only two seats
别急  蟹老板
Calm your waters, Mr. Krabs
我亲手来改装
I modified this little baby myself
你确定现在小伙子都开这种车吗
Are you sure this is
what the kids are driving these days?
酷小子才开
Only the cool kids
你们一定是迷路了吧
You guys must be lost
笨蛋大道就在附近呢
Doofus Drive is around the corner
没迷路
We're not lost
我带了指南针
I've got my compass
再见了  白痴
So long, dorks
再见  兄弟
Good-bye, pals
说这种话的早被咱打得满地找牙了
We used to beat people up for saying things like that
好一个倒反天罡
Everything's all topsy-turvy now
洗刷刷
我们到了
Here we are
洗刷刷
The Wash
这种俱乐部取名越来越离谱了
They sure are giving these clubs some crazy names
不得不跟你们说
I have to tell you boys
我有点紧张
I'm a little nervous
我已经  就是
I haven't been, you know
没登场好一段时间了
"on the scene" for quite a while now
跟着我们玩就行了  蟹老板
Just follow our lead, Mr. Krabs
尤其就是要
And above all
冷静耍酷
keep it cool
酷
Cool
明白
Gotcha
大家好
Hello, gang
海绵宝宝回来了
SpongeBob's back
一起狂欢吧
Let's party
不管怎样我都行
Any port in a stor
等一下
Wait a minute
这就是家洗衣店
This is a Laundromat
好耶
Oh, yeah
这样才叫像话
That's what I'm talking about
太好了
Oh, yeah, yeah
色彩缤纷
The colors
好耶
Yeah
还要看洗衣服吗
You guys want another rinse cycle?
我买单
I'm buying
跟你们说吧
You know
虽说我跟大伙儿一样爱看衣服  但是
I love staring at delicates as much as the next guy, but
就只是  夜生活得多来点花样吧
it's just that, I thought we'd see more of the nightlife
至少也让我
Something that will give me
好好疯一把  热血沸腾起来
that wild and crazy, hot-blooded feeling
懂我的意思吧
if you know what I mean
我当然懂了  蟹老板
I know what you mean, Mr. Krabs
今晚咱们才刚刚开始放纵呢
This is only stop numero uno on our night of debauchery
放纵
Debauchery
Debauchery?
都没想过
I never thought
高架底下捡垃圾哪热血沸腾了
of picking up trash under the highway as hot-blooded
不过既然小伙子都很投入
But if it's what the kids are into
你感觉到
So are you feeling
自己在疯一把了没  蟹老板
that wild and crazy feeling, Mr. Krabs?
还没
Not yet
放心  迟早会的
Don't worry, you will
你感觉到了没  蟹老板
Are you feeling it now, Mr. Krabs?
感觉到哪里热热的
I'm feeling a warm spot
抱歉
Sorry
便宜货超市
你感觉到了没  蟹老板
Are you feeling it now, Mr. Krabs?
感觉到了没
Are you feeling it?
我感觉到了  海绵宝宝
I'm feeling it, SpongeBob
派大星  那个不能玩
Patrick, that's not a ride
给我下去
Get off of me
你感觉到了没  蟹老板
Are you feeling it now, Mr. Krabs?
汝有感乎  蟹掌柜
Art thou feeling it now, Mr. Krabs?
感觉到了没  蟹老板
You feeling it now, Mr. Krabs?
那现在呢
How about now?
兔兔屋
感觉到了吗  蟹老板
Can you feel it, Mr. Krabs?
所以说  你们想知道我感觉到了没
So, you want to know if I can feel it?
想
Yeah
真的想知道我感觉到了没
Do you really want to know if I can feel it?
特想
Yeah, yeah
因为我感觉得到
Because I can feel it
想知道我感觉到什么了吗
You want to know what I'm feeling?
想
Yes
我感觉自己就像是个二百五
I'm feeling like a total barnacle-head
你们觉得这很酷吗
You think this is cool?
那这样呢
How about this
这样呢
And this
潮不潮
Am I with it now?
都乐得这么明显了还看不出来吗
You guys wouldn't know a good time
if it bit you in the aft end
我回去了
I'm going home
你们一点都不酷
You guys ain't cool
你们很逊
You're lame
逊吗
Lame?
逊
Lame
是呆子
You're nerds
土包子
Geeks
讨厌鬼
Creeps
外加幼稚鬼
And babies
怎么会幼稚
Not babies
就算我老归老
I may be old, but even an old bag of shells like me
也知道你们整晚一件酷事都没做出来
knows that you haven't suggested
one cool thing all night
祝你们晚安
So good night to ya
那你就要错过偷内裤了
I guess you're going to miss the panty raid
什么
The what?
我说
I said
那你就要错过偷内裤了
I guess you're going to miss the panty raid
偷内裤
Panty raid?
你说的是女的吧
You're talking about girls, right?
就那种女生
Girl girls?
没错
Yeah
你是说要翻箱倒柜
And you're talking about raiding their dressers
偷内裤对吧
for their underpants, right?
没错
Oh, yeah
那就算我一个
Well, count me in
大功告成我就收回刚刚说的话
If this works, I'll take back what I said
不当你们逊了
about you two being lame
不逊
Not lame
这还差不多
Now, this is more like it
相信我们吧  老头子
Give us some credit, old man
偷内裤我们是专业的
We're panty professionals
每次都专偷这家
We score here all the time
蕾丝内裤
Frilly things
中大奖了
We hit the jackpot
好耶  蟹老板
Oh, yeah, Mr. Krabs
你们还真帮我大功告成了
You finally came through for me, boys
感觉自己又重返青春了
I feel young again
尤金
Eugene?
老妈
Mother?
你拿我裤子干什么
What are you doing with my bloomers?
那个
Well
我
I, uh
怎么不早说要偷我妈家
Why didn't you tell me this was my mother's house?
你也没问啊
Why didn't you ask?
都是海绵宝宝跟派大星一手策划的
But it was all SpongeBob and Patrick's idea
跟我回房间去
Go to your room, mister
天亮之前都不准出门
You're grounded for the rest of the night
好的  老妈
Yes, Mommy
没事  老爷爷
Don't worry, pops
你房间就快到了
We're almost to your room
抱歉  蟹老板
Sorry, Mr. Krabs
没事  小子
That's all right, lad
我确实感觉重返青春了
I certainly feel younger
晚安  蟹老板
Good night, Mr. Krabs
晚安  海绵宝宝
Good night, SpongeBob
尤金  熄灯
Eugene, lights out
好的  老妈
Yes, Mommy